

CONTACT



Munich, Germany



eunice.igbinedion@yahoo.com



+4915211837442



https://www.linkedin.com/in/euniceigbinedion/



https://github.com/Eunnylans



https://eunice-igbinedionportfolio.netlify.app/



https://saudijournals.com/media/articles/SJEF_68_272-280.pdf

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript React.js Node.js
Python SQL Typo3
HTML5 NoSQL Git
CSS3 Contentful GitHub

OTHER SKILLS

Marketing Strategy Service Support Analytical thinking Problem-solving Teamwork

Sales Team Support Digital Marketing Creativity Time management Marketing Research

Jira

Scrum UX/UI

Figma

COURSES & CERTIFICATION

SAP ERP Techlabs Salesforce/CRM Google Analytics Digital Marketing

LANGUAGES

English Deutsch Native Speaker(C2) Intermediate(B1)

INTEREST

Learning Travelling Dancing Research

EUNICE ABIEYUWA IGBINEDION

WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Result-driven web developer, resourceful at contributing to highly collaborative work environments, determining customer satisfaction, and finding solutions are my core competencies. Skillful in developing customer-focused and sustainable websites. Built apps that met the highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices, and speed. Developed web applications across multiple APIs, third-party integrations, and databases.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DEVELOPER

Regenate (Working Student) | Mar 2022 - Sep 2022

- Revamped web application, minimizing hacker attacks from 2.3% to 0.02%
- Designed and developed a user-friendly website, including an optimized check-out page that increased user clicks and, subsequently, increased the number of registered persons by 15%
- Researched new technologies, software packages, and hardware products for use in website projects

MARKETING SUPERVISOR

Websolutions & Communications Nig Ltd | Jan 2017 - Sep 2018

- Supported Premium business teams to align their strategies and executions to the brand increasing revenue by 40%
- Collaborated with other relevant functions to develop strategies that drive the Premium brand vision and objectives
- Researched and analyzed market trends, competitor offerings, demographics, and other information that affects marketing strategies. This action resulted in surpassing the 2018 target by 33%
- Improved Seo, and social media marketing

SALES SERVICES SUPERVISOR

Euromega Atlantic Nig Ltd | Jun 2014 - Dec 2016

- Managed and tracked project budgets to ensure effective deployment was spent in line with budget
- Processed work tools, sales float, expenses, incentives, and all concerns for field sales personnel, were resolved on time, minimizing sales impediments from 10.3% to 0.7%
- Dedicatedly pitched new ideas to solve business challenges.

SALES ADMIN

Eko Supreme Resources Nig Ltd | Aug 2010 - Jun 2014

- Initiated and tracked orders to completion
- Ensured a clear & consistent level of communication was upheld
- Met and surpassed yearly sales target by 28%

OFFICE ASSISTANT

Birnin Magaji Local Govt | Jun 2009 - Jul 2010

- Administrative role
- Achieved 100% compliance

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

WBS Coding School, Berlin (Germany) | May 2022 - Sep 2022

• 15-week full-time project-based coding training

MA Science & Technology Studies | Sept 2020 - Oct 2023

Technical University of Munich

MBA (Marketing Specialisation) | Oct 2016 - Sep 2018

University of Lagos

BSC Economics & Statistics | Oct 2004 - Sep 2008

University of Benin